MARCO DOMINGUES | SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

Address: NW8 London

Telephone: +44 (0) 7 840 399 131

Email: marcodomingues.md@gmail.com

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/marco-domingues-774660187/

PERSONAL PROFILE

A highly motivated entry-level software developer, I have dedicated the past 2 years learning and practicing front and back end development. A hard working, driven individual with excellent communication and interpersonal skills. Flexible and organized with strong problem solving abilities who is able to work effectively under pressure and pay attention to details.

Am currently looking for a software developer opportunity that will allow me to work alongside an expert team of developers.

IT / TECHNICAL SKILLS

- Languages: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, C#, Python, Java
- Frameworks: ReactJS, SASS, .NET
- Other: Visual Studio, Firebase, Unity, Blender

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Miki Travel Limited London **VIP Group Operations Agent** March 2018 - Nov 2020

- Analysing needs and negotiating the best interests for the clients in order to exceed their expectations.
- Ad Hoc tours: VIP, MICE and other special tours.
- Outbound market: Asia.
- Inbound market: Portugal, France, Italy.

Novotel London Paddington London **Front Office Supervisor**

Nov 2015 - March 2018

- Creating a fantastic first impression with a warm and personalized welcome.
- Supporting the team on shift to obtain the same results.
- During my experience as supervisor had the opportunity to train 2 new teams together with 2 other supervisors.

Novotel Convention et Wellness Paris

Sep 2014 - Nov 2015

Front Office Team Member

Taking care of guest from their arrival through to their departure.

EDUCATION AND QUALIFICATIONS

CFA Trajectoire, Paris

Sept 2013 – Aug 2014

• Reception Apprenticeship – Hospitality and tourism

Escola Secundaria De Rocha Peixoto, Portugal

Sept 2006 - Jul 2010

• High School Graduate

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

Other courses:

The Training Room

- CIW: Advanced HTML5 and CSS3 Specialist
- MTA: Basics of Python Programming
- MTA: Software Development Fundamentals (Course & Lab)
- OCA: Java SE 8 Programmer I
- OCP Java SE 8 Programmer II

LANGUAGES

- Portuguese
- English
- French
- Spanish

INTERESTS

- Software Development
- Playing with Unity and Blender
- Computer Games
- Travel
- Sport
- Movies

REFERENCES AVAILABLE UPON REQUEST